### Formulaic is a PowerShell module for math, physics, and statistics functions.   

It contains several somewhat useful functions to take the tedium out of math.

You can use Formulaic to:

* Convert from Royal Measurements to Metric
* Convert celsius to farenheit, and visa-versa
* Calculate angles in a triangle
* Get the area and circumference of a circle
* Do simple math flashcards
* Get the areas and perimeters of squares, rectangles, and trapezoids
* Get averages and standard deviations for a set of numbers
* Get the correlation coeffecient of properties within a set of data
* Measure mass and velocity
* Run open-ended calculations

Formulaic is also open-source, so you can check out the code and use it to create your own calculators.

Formulaic is published with [PowerShell Pipeworks](http://powershellpipeworks.com) as a web site and service, with a companion Windows app.
 
